50 years have passed.
But I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
Yet the suffering continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Got to get back --
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
Oh!
Hello, little friend.
I don't suppose you know
if there is a time portal
atop this mountain, do you?
No?
Yes?
Aku has destroyed many.
I worry that
there are none left.
Phew!
That was close!
I didn't think
you'd get here so fast.
Fool!
Oh, fun fact --
that was the last remaining
time portal in existence!
Ooh, so angry!
Be careful, Samurai --
so much stress
will give you a heart attack.
Ooh!
What am I saying?
Please continue!
Never mind what I said!
Whoa!
Ho, ho!
Not so fast, Samurai.
I know better than
to mess with that sword!
But before I go,
I'll leave you
someone to play with.
And so...
I was not able to find it again.
There!
We are here.
It's not here.
Could someone else
have taken it?
No.
I realize now that...
I did not
lose the sword...
but the sword left me.
Thank you, friend.
Yes, thank you.
I do not know
how long this may take.
I'll go with you.
You cannot.
It is something that
I must do on my own.
Wait, I...
Oh.
I guess I'll just...
wait here.
Are you lost?
Yes.
Good.
Come make tea.
Hold it.
Where do you
think you're going?
Up the mountain,
to kill the Samurai.
What's it to you?
I'm going to stop you.
Hey, why have we
stopped? What's so funny?
It's a girl!
She says
she's going to stop us.
What did he say?
Something about
a squirrel.
I love squirrels!
Is it lunch already?
So a little thing like you
is gonna stop
this whole army, huh?
Yep.
We're gonna rip you apart
in a bunch of pieces,
and then we're gonna
take those pieces
and rip them apart
into even more pieces!
I'm waiting.
Hmm.
- Huh?
Mother?
I knew you would fail us.
You were the strongest,
but the most unfocused.
Always distracted,
questioning everything.
But all that can change.
You can still honor
our Lord Father.
Destroy the Samurai,
Ashi.
No.
You were wrong
about everything.
Jack showed me
the truth.
Then you, too, will die.
How could you
betray your family?
He killed your sisters!
And you let him live!
No, you killed them!
We were made
for one purpose --
to kill!
Our fate was sealed
the day we were born!
The Samurai
is our mortal enemy.
He must die
at any cost.
No.
This is terrible.
Really?
Yes.
Yes, quite terrible.
This tea has all
the necessary ingredients...
but it lacks
the most important one --
balance.
I see why your path to the sword
remains clouded.
This isn't the path?!
I don't understand.
Then you must
show me the way!
I cannot.
It is not for me
to show you your path.
That's fortune cookie
nonsense!
He knows where it is.
He just won't tell you.
Please,
you must tell me.
That is something
you must earn.
Earn?!
After everything
we've done,
everything
we've been through --
the death, the loss,
the suffering!
Who are you to deny us
what is rightfully ours!?
Enough.
We have lost the sword
because of you.
I have kept us alive!
He's the one
who has taken it from us!
He knows where it is!
No.
I've let you consume me
for far too long.
You're in my way.
You.
You are the one who has
kept the past hidden.
Your anger,
your frustration.
You're a fool!
You have blinded us,
but now I can see.
You need me!
Now you are balanced.
Like your father,
you have been chosen.
To stop a force of
ultimate evil.
You are worthy.
Ashi.
Jack?
Yes.
It is me.
You got your sword.
And a shave
and a haircut.
Hmm, yes.
And you...
you have been
very busy.
Ow.
Thank you.
So, what next?
Aku!
* Watch out
* Got to get back,
back to the past *
* Samurai Jack
* Watch out
* Got to get back,
back to the past *
* Samurai Jack
* Watch out
* Jack, Jack,
Jack, Jack, Jack *
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Samurai Jack
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack